(Sheldon:)What if it's banditos
shooting at us?
(Sheldon:)What if we get kidnapped?
(Sheldon:)What if we end up in a factory
making Bart Simpson piñatas
for the rest of our lives?!
It's the tire.
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)I am getting too old
for this crud.
(Bernadette:)Amy, I noticed
your status still says
"in a relationship"
on Facebook.
(Amy:)You're right.
(Amy:)I should probably let
all of my Facebook friends know.
(Amy:)Penny, I'm no longer
in a relationship.
(Bernadette:)Did you change yours
to "married" yet?
(Penny:)Uh, no, not yet.
(Penny:)There's still a few people
I haven't told personally.
(Amy:)Who?
(Penny:)Oh, just my parents
(Penny:)and my entire family.
(clears throat)
(Leonard:)What?
(Penny:)Why?
(Penny:)Well, I don't want
to hurt my dad.
(Penny:)You know, he always wanted
(Penny:)to dance with his daughter
at her wedding.
(Bernadette:)What about
your sister's wedding?
(Penny:)They started to,
then her water broke.
(Penny:)You know, if he finds out
we eloped,
(Penny:)it's gonna break his heart.